=Seal of Love= (Season 1)
= ختم الحب = (الموسم الأول)
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
Master.
يتقن.
How was that possible?
كيف كان ذلك ممكنا؟
The Demon-killing Spell didn't hurt her at all.
تعويذة قتل الشياطين لم تؤذيها على الإطلاق.
Master,
يتقن،
there must be something fishy with her.
يجب أن يكون هناك شيء مريب معها.
(At nine tomorrow morning, see you on the Immortal Spirit Platform.)
(في التاسعة صباح الغد ، أراك على منصة الروح الخالدة).
(At eleven tomorrow morning,
(في الحادية عشرة من صباح الغد ، أراك على منصة الروح الخالدة.)
He's fast.
إنه سريع.
The Demon-trapping Formation has been out of service for a century.
كان تشكيل اصطياد الشياطين خارج الخدمة لمدة قرن.
Goddess, I've reinforced it for you.
يا إلهة ، لقد عززتها من أجلك.
No matter what kind of demon she is,
بغض النظر عن نوع الشيطان هي ،
she won't be able to get away.
لن تكون قادرة على الابتعاد.
Wait.
انتظر.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
Don't get your delicate skin scratched.
لا تخدش بشرتك الرقيقة.
We're not sure
لسنا متأكدين
how powerful the Demon Queen is.
ما مدى قوة ملكة الشيطان.
If this formation fails to trap her,
إذا فشل هذا التكوين في حبسها ،
you and I will be doomed.
أنت وأنا سنهزم.
Look at that.
انظر إلى ذلك.
It's the center of the Formation.
إنه مركز التكوين.
The greatest feature is that it greatly amplifies the power.
أعظم ميزة هي أنها تضخم القوة بشكل كبير.
All we need to do is put some power into the center.
كل ما علينا فعله هو وضع بعض القوة في المركز.
The Formation will amplify it a thousand times
سيضخمها التكوين ألف مرة
and attack the demon with the power.
وهاجم الشيطان بالقوة.
What do you think now?
ما رأيك الآن؟
Yuan.
يوان.
Master.
يتقن.
Good. You're recovering quickly.
جيد.  أنت تتعافى بسرعة.
All you need is the Immortal Spirit Fruit.
كل ما تحتاجه هو فاكهة الروح الخالدة.
Thank you, Master, for your Shangqing Knack.
شكرا لك يا معلمة على موهبتك في Shangqing.
Mm.
مم.
You're so honey-lipped.
أنت شفتين العسل.
Unlike the boring Lord Qing Chen.
على عكس اللورد تشينغ تشن الممل.
He always pulls a long face.
هو دائما يسحب وجها طويلا.
Master, you haven't tasted my lips.
سيدي ، أنت لم تذوق شفتي.
How do you know I'm honey-lipped?
كيف تعرف أنني شفاه العسل؟
Naughty boy,
ولد مشاغب،
how dare you flirt with your master!
كيف تجرؤ على مغازلة سيدك!
Do your cultivation carefully.
قم بزراعتك بعناية.
Tomorrow, I'll get back the Immortal Spirit Fruit to you.
غدا ، سأعيد لك فاكهة الروح الخالدة.
Mm.
مم.
(At eleven tomorrow morning, see you on the Immortal Spirit Platform.)
(في الحادية عشرة من صباح الغد ، أراك على منصة الروح الخالدة.)
Oh, try to catch me with such a rubbish formation?
أوه ، حاول الإمساك بي بمثل هذا تكوين القمامة؟
Humph, Wicked Demon! You're dying, you know?
همف ، شرير شرير!  أنت تحتضر ، هل تعلم؟
Do I even know you?
هل اعرفك اصلا؟
You're a demon, but you try to marry Lord Qing Chen.
أنت شيطان ، لكنك تحاول الزواج من اللورد تشينغ تشن.
In our sect,
في طائفتنا ،
no demons can live.
لا يمكن أن تعيش الشياطين.
Don't let her get to you in case you get hurt.
لا تدعها تصل إليك في حالة تعرضك للأذى.
Oh, I see. You sound quite jealous.
حسنا أرى ذلك.  تبدو غيورًا جدًا.
So, you're my rival in love.
إذن ، أنت منافسي في الحب.
Prepare to die.
استعد للموت.
Aah!
آآآه!
What's going on now?
ما يحدث الآن؟
Our power isn't enough. We underestimated her.
قوتنا ليست كافية.  قللنا من شأنها.
You're so weak. Don't bother to be immortals.
أنت ضعيف جدا.  لا تهتم بأن تكون خالداً.
Come be my disciples.
تعالوا كونوا تلاميذي.
She isn't an ordinary demon.
إنها ليست شيطانًا عاديًا.
Her power is unmeasurable.
قوتها لا تقاس.
I'm afraid we need the strength of a hundred years
أخشى أننا نحتاج إلى قوة مائة عام
to fill the center.
لملء المركز.
Strength of a hundred years?
قوة مائة عام؟
Aah!
آآآه!
(Fusheng...)
(فوشينغ ...)
♪In the next life May everything be in peace♪
في الحياة الآخرة ، عسى أن يكون كل شيء في سلام
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪ العودة في مسقط رأس الهواجس باقية ♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love I just can't get over it♪
♪ أسعى وراء الحب النحيف الذي لا يمكنني تجاوزه
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪